steelconstruction.info 2016-11-19

# Privacy policy - Steelconstruction.info

### From Steelconstruction.info

The following are the terms of the Privacy Policy to which you agree by using or accessing SteelConstruction.info. 

## [top] Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information given via www.steelconstruction.info (the "Site") by you, the user or users of the Site, to us (“User Information”). "We/Us" means the British Constructional Steelwork Association, the owners of the Site, and the Steel Construction Institute. We process personal data only in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and associated legislation and we will not disclose your User Information to any person without your express consent, unless required to do so by law. 

### [top] Data Collection

When using the Site, you will only be asked to enter User Information when creating an account or logging into the Site. The User Information will only be used for the purposes stated at the collection point and/or in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By entering your User Information, you accept that we may retain and use your User Information. We may perform statistical analyses of users’ behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various areas of the Site. 

### [top] Data Use

We shall be entitled to use your User Information in order to identify your membership of the British Constructional Steelwork Association and/or the Steel Construction Institute. We shall also be entitled to use your User Information to inform you of marketing notifications if you have requested this when creating an account. 

### [top] Information about our use of cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. 

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. 

We use the following types of cookies: 

  * **Strictly necessary cookies**  
These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website or use a shopping cart. 
  * **Analytical/performance cookies**  
They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. 
  * **Functionality cookies**  
These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region). 

Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.
